我记得小时候
I remember when I was a little girl,
爸爸带我去马戏团
my dada took me to the circus --
那是世界上最棒的演出
The greatest show on earth.
有好多小丑  大象  会跳舞的熊
There were clowns and elephants and dancing bears...
还有一个穿粉色紧身衣的漂亮女士
And a beautiful lady in pink tights
高高地在我们头顶上飞来飞去
flew high above our heads.
我坐在下面观看时
And as I sat there watching,
总有一种少了点什么的感觉
I had the feeling that something was missing.
我不知道是什么
I don't know what,
但表演结束时
but when it was all over,
我对自己说
I said to myself,
"马戏团就只是仅此而已吗"
"Is that all there is to the circus?"
大事不好  麻烦来了
Uh-oh. Here comes trouble.
我知道你对自己说的话
I know what you must be saying to yourselves
"如果她真是这么感觉的话
"If that's the way she feels about it
为何她还要待在这里"
Why doesn't she just end it all?"
不
Oh, no
他一言不发
Cat's got his tongue.
我还没准备好迎接那最终的失望
I'm not ready yet for that final disappointment.
因为我知道  我站在这里跟你对话
For I know just as well as I'm standing here talking to you,
当最后一刻来临
when that final moment comes
当我咽下最后一口气
and I'm breathing my last breath...
我会对自己说  "仅此而已吗
...I'll be saying to myself, "Is that all?
死亡就是仅此而已吗"
Is that all there is to dying?"
亲爱的  你不会还在生的我的气吧
Baby, you're not still mad at me, are you?
有吗
Are you?
没有  没事了
No, it's okay.
真的  没事了
Really, it's fine.
我忍不住不告诉他们
I just couldn't not tell them. You know?
我知道
I know.
我当时太兴奋了
I mean, I just get so excited.
现在也很兴奋
Am excited.
又幸福
Happy.
我也很高兴  小泰  真的
I'm glad, Teddy. Me too.
是吗
Yeah?
当然了
Of course I am.
都有点小激动了
Getting excited a little bit.
这是上帝的旨意  不是吗
I mean, God's will, right?
是啊
Yes.
我爱你  托妮
I love you, Tawney.
我知道
I know you do.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
是吗
Do you?
我真的爱你  小泰
I do love you, Teddy.
天哪
Jesus.
你怎么知道我住这里
How'd you even know where I lived?
白页上找的
White pages.
这样啊
Oh, yeah.
那些东西真是
Those.
万物的生存和毁灭真是神奇啊  对不对
It's amazing what survives and what doesn't, isn't it?
确实
It is.
该死
Well, shit.
你来干什么  丹尼尔
What can I do for you, Daniel?
我也不知道为什么今天来
I'm not sure why today exactly,
但是...
but, uh...
我想来见你
I wanted to come and see you.
是吗
Is that right?
跟你说声不要生气
To say "No hard feelings."
好啊
All right.
没问题  哥们
Sure, buddy.
谢谢
Thanks.
你一路骑自行车过来的吗
You huff it all the way over here?
其实不远
It's not that far.
也不近吧
Not that close, either.
你还有什么其他地方要去吗
Got anyplace else you're supposed to be?
那就快点进屋吧
Then get your ass on inside.
他们给你喝葡萄苏打水了吗
Did they give you grape soda?
谁
Who?
警察
The police.
那晚
That night.
"那晚"
"That night"?
丹尼尔  你就这么直奔主题吗
Well, damn, Daniel, you just jumping right in, huh?
我不知道  哥们
I'm not even sure, man.
我已经不去怎么想它了
I don't think on it too much anymore.
好吧
Okay.
你渴吗
You thirsty?
这是我妻子办教堂活动买的
My wife got these for a church thing she had over here.
一直占着冰箱
They've been clogging up the fridge.
反正是周一早上
I figure, hey, it's Monday morning.
成人不妨也来瓶柠檬水喝吧
Might as well have an adult lemonade.
我们用这个玩过特库摩保龄球
We played tecmo bowl on this.
可不是吗
You're damn right we did.
确实
Yeah.
我们结婚时我父母送给我们的
My parents gave it to us when we got married.
一直就放在这里
It anchors the room.
话说
So, uh...
里面什么样子  兄弟
what was it like in there, man?
我总得问问你  对吧
I mean, I got to ask. Right?
很封闭
Confining.
应该就是这样吧
That would be the word for it, I suppose.
一定程度上很封闭  但是...
Confining in some ways, but...
你跟乔治还有联系吗
Do you still talk to George?
怎么可能
Damn, that's a sequitur.
乔治
George?
George.
我很久没有看到老乔治...
I haven't seen old George in...
我们几年前一起去火石河那边钓过鱼
Well, we went fishing together a couple years ago on the Flint.
没想到你竟然提到他
Funny you mention him, though.
我好像给他打过电话
Thought I might give him a call.
好像给他打过还是确实打过
Thought you'd give him a call or you gave him a call?
别这样  大律师
Easy there, counselor.
不要这样咄咄逼人
Don't go poking me in the chest with no question marks.
我给他打过电话
I gave him a call.
出于礼貌
To be nice.
但他没理会我
Hadn't heard back.
他现在住在哪里
Where's he live now?
这玩意儿真难喝  你想喝啤酒吗
Oh, these are terrible. You want a beer?
乔治住在佛罗里达
Uh... Georgey lives in Florida.
利夫奥克
Live Oak.
那里热死了
Satan's butthole, man.
你不会想伤害他吧
You ain't thinking about hurting him, are you?
我不想伤害任何人
I don't want to hurt anybody.
我可不想被牵涉到那种事上
'Cause I wouldn't want to be a part of anything like that.
什么事
Part of what?
但你要去拜访他的话  代我问好
But if you go visit him, tell him I said "Hello."
我会的
I will.
去拜访他还是代我问好
Go visit him or tell him I said "Hello"?
两者都会吧
Both, I suppose.
我不确定
I'm not sure.
我该走了
I should go.
等等  我说...
Hey. Hey, that's, uh...
利夫奥克离这里很远  哥们
That's a long ride down to Live Oak, buddy.
我会想办法
I'll figure it out.
跟你说吧
I'll tell you what.
其实今早我该去上班的
I'm supposed to be at a job this morning,
可那家伙就是个贱人
But he's a cheap son of a bitch, really.
要不  我们一起去公路旅行吧
What say... We go on a road trip?
我们要先给他打电话吗
Should we call him first?
那晚...
Look, that night --
或者是那天早上  警察在场...
Or that morning, I mean, with the police --
我只是说  你跟她在争吵
All I did was say you and her were arguing.
仅此而已
That's it.
是乔治说...
It was George who said --
该死
Hell.
你想去跟他谈谈这件事的话
You want to go down there, you want to talk with him about it,
只要你不动粗...
as long as you keep it gentlemanly...
我乐意开车
...I am happy to do the driving.
好了
All right.
把你的小自行车搬到车上
Put your little bicycle in the bed there,
你去坐副驾驶
and you grab shotgun.
我去方便一下
I'm gonna piss real quick.
然后我们就一起上路  哥们
And then we'll hit the road, son!
收好小桌板  各位乘客
Tray tables up, passengers.
准备起飞了
Prepare for takeoff.
我有那个的优惠券
I-I got one for that.
好啊
Figured you might.
一共41.2美元
Your total is $41.20.
一
One...
二
Two...
三
Three...
四
Four...
五
Five...
六
Six...
七
Seven...
八张1块的
Eight $1s.
这儿有10块呢
Oh, there's that $10.
看到了
Yep. There it is.
还有20
And...$20.
-现在有...  -38块
- That's... - $38.
38块
$38?
-那我还差...  -差3块2
- So I'm... - $3.20 short.
3块2
$3.20...?
还差3块2
Short.
我真不愿意用这些  但是...
I hate to use these, but...
我不知道这是否...
I don't even know if that...
您还差20美分
You still owe 20 cents.
我记得我这儿有25美分的
I know I have a quarter in here.
是枚弗吉尼亚州纪念币
It's a Virginia one.
-上面刻着"詹姆斯敦"的  -算了
- Got Jamestown on it. - Forget it.
老天  算了吧
God. Forget it.
我替你付这20美分  不用麻烦了
I will pay the 20 cents. Not a problem, okay?
真是出人意料啊
What do you know?
詹姆斯敦
Jamestown.
这样就对了
That's right... right there.
谢谢你花钱买了这些
Appreciate you flipping the bill for those.
味道不错
Tastes good.
可不  很不错
Yeah, as good as it gets.
老兄  这是真的吗
Oh, man. Unreal.
-我是说  不可思议  -什么
- I mean, damn! - What?
你个狗崽子
You son of a bitch!
今天早上我从床上爬起来的时候
When I got out of bed this morning
我从衣柜上方的小窗户往外看
and I was staring out that little window above our commode
盯着39号公路上的交通灯
at the traffic light that's out on 39
就是草地那边那个永远亮着绿灯的交通灯
that is always green out beyond the hayfield,
我绝对想不到  就在今天
I never would have said, "Well, today's the day
我要和丹尼尔·霍顿一起去佛罗里达
that I'm gonna go to Florida with Daniel G.D. Holden."
绝对想不到
I mean, never.
那个交通灯永远是绿灯吗
The light's always green?
反正我从没见过它变红灯
I ain't never seen it red.
一次也没有
Not once.
那它为什么在那儿
Why's it there?
有些事儿  你就是无法预料的
Some things, you just don't see coming.
我想你说得对
I think you're right.
我就是对的
I am right.
但我很高兴和你一路前行
But I'm glad to be sitting here with you.
感觉不错
Feels right.
感觉像是我们有地方可去
Feels like we're... going somewhere.
男女之间的那些妙不可言的一切
Everything that is good between men and women
都已融入泥浆和黄油
was written in mud and butter,
还有烤肉酱中
and barbecue sauce.
-你听过吗  -没有
- You know? - No.
有次我做梦  保拉·迪恩在梦里对我说的
Paula Deen said that to me in a dream I had one time.
谁是保拉·迪恩
Who's Paula Deen?
她是电视节目里的一位厨师
Oh, she's a chef on TV.
她曾经是
Well, she was.
不知道怎么搞的  现在厨师们都上电视了
Chefs are on TV now, for some reason.
大家都很喜欢看
People eat it up.
她就是个乔治亚州奥尔巴尼出来的大火腿
Anyway, she's just a big ol' ham hock out of Albany, G.A.
她给北方佬做南方菜
She makes southern food for Yankees.
我的重点是  在我的梦里
My point is, in my dream,
不知怎的  我和她一起玩激流划艇
I'm white-water rafting with her, for some reason,
她对我讲了那番话
and, um, she said that to me...
就在她碰我的小弟弟之前
Right before she... touched my hamster.
这真是让我难以忘怀  你懂吗
but it stuck with me, you know?
只有这个梦给我这种感觉
It's the only thing from a dream that ever has.
你经常做梦吗
Do you dream often?
不是  几乎从不做梦
No. Almost never.
我认为我的睡眠质量比所有见过的人都好
I think I sleep more soundly than anybody I ever met.
我敢肯定如此
In fact, I know I do.
倒是你看起来像是经常做梦的人
Now, you seem the type that does a lot of dreaming.
有时候吧
Well, sometimes.
你醒了以后会回想那些梦吗
You wake up and think about them?
那对我来说就是浪费时间
Seems like a waste of time to me.
思考它们是一种浪费吗
A waste to think on them?
当你一觉醒来  回到现实的时候  是的
Once you're awake and walking around in the real world, yeah.
我是说你有现实的事情要去处理
I mean, once there are things to actually take care of.
我不知道
I don't know.
试图从梦境中找到意义所在
Trying to find meaning in them...
试图从任何事情里找到意义所在
trying to find meaning in anything.
如果你当真了  那就是浪费时间
It's a waste of time, if you really want to get down to it.
那么生活是毫无意义的吗
So life's meaningless?
谁的生活
Whose life?
我想  是所有人的生活吧
Anybody's life, I suppose.
这不正是你想表达的意思吗
Isn't that what you're saying?
老兄  你像个娘们儿一样曲解事实
Damn, man, you twist things around like a woman.
塔拉哈西[美国佛罗里达州首府]
湖城
永利刚才气疯了
Wynn was mad.
不是吗
Wasn't she?
她没有人情味  你知道的
She all corporate, you know?
她会没事儿的
She'll be all right.
是啊  可我不喜欢那样
Yeah, but I don't like being like that.
我已经很久没抽大麻了
It's been too long since I smoked.
的确  很久了
Exactly... too long.
不  是久到不会再抽了
No, too long to do it again.
这玩意儿曾搞得我人仰马翻
That'd put me on my ass.
搞得你人仰马翻吗  真是个坏东西啊
That such a bad thing... out your head and on your ass?
真是难以置信
Can't believe this.
我已经32岁了
32 years old.
在平价商店的停车场里抽大麻
Smoking weed in the Thrifty Town parking lot
而且还是我打工的地方
where I actually friggin' work.
怎么会这样呢
How did this happen?
就是这样
There it is.
看看这些闪亮的金属物件就知道
Just follow the shiny metal things.
女士优先
After you, my lady.
我以前从来没买过轮胎
I've never bought tires before.
它们好像一直就在车上似的
They've always just... been there.
收银机以前是摆在这里的
The register used to be right here.
爸爸会在这儿放一个超大号的金属手电筒
Dad would keep one of those big-ass metal flashlights right here,
万一有需要  他就抡起来揍某人
just in case he'd need to take a swing at anyone.
下周和我确认下  到时候应该有你要的货
Check in with me next week. I should have that in for you.
感谢您惠顾波林轮胎
Thank you for shopping at Paulie Tire.
希望您再度光临
I hope you come back again.
再见
Bye.
阿曼莎
Amantha?
你们俩今天打算干什么啊
What are... what are y'all up to today?
你好  小泰  希望我们没有打扰你
Hey, Teddy. Hope we're not bothering you.
我只是无法想象你俩来这儿是为了买轮胎
Well, I can't imagine you're here for tires.
再次恭喜你们有了宝宝
Congratulations again about the baby.
真心恭喜
Seriously.
谢谢你
Thank you. Yeah.
这是阿丽莎
This is Alesha.
这里就是轮胎店
And this is the tire store.
我是她的继弟
I'm the stepbrother.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
我们马上就不给你添乱了
We'll get out of your hair in just a second.
我只是想带她参观下
I just wanted to show her around.
我已经很久没来这儿了
I haven't been here in so long.
闻起来一切依旧
It smells the same.
这种味道很好闻
It's a good smell.
对此我想了很多
I think about that a lot.
闻起来始终是一成不变
Always smells the dang same.
我跟阿丽莎说
I told Alesha
我们的自动售货机秒杀其它所有自动售货机
that we have the vending machine to beat all vending machines.
这是事实
That's true.
我们有巧克力和花生酱的特趣巧克力
We have the chocolate and peanut butter Twix,
所以
So...
她想要钥匙
She'd like the keys.
可以  没问题
Oh. Yeah. All right.
这里就像查理的巧克力工厂
It's like Wonka's Factory,
只是四周都是轮辋
but with rims.
谢谢你  小泰
Thank you, Teddy.
小事一桩
No problem.
好了
Okay.
-你想要哪个  -4号  谢谢
- What would you like? - Number 4, please.
给你
Here you go.
好的  我还想要那个
Okay, okay. I would like that one, too.
下午好  斯特恩先生
Good afternoon, Mr. Stern.
下午好
Good afternoon.
我半个小时后要出席一个陪审团
I am on a panel in half an hour.
需要突击做些准备
Need to do a little cramming.
很抱歉  我没有多少时间帮您准备
I'm sorry... I don't have much time to help you prep.
几个小时后  我就上飞机了
I'm supposed to be on a plane in a couple of hours.
这虽不是正式的
This is nothing official yet,
但是我今天要求和你见面
but I asked you to meet me here today
因为我现在愿意...
Because I am now willing...
虽然勉强  但是愿意
begrudgingly, but willing
就丹尼尔·霍顿认罪协议的可能性进行讨论
to discuss the possibility of a plea deal for Daniel Holden.
我洗耳恭听
I'm all ears.
已服刑期上加刑10年  15年以上缓刑
Time served plus 10, 15 more probation.
他不会回到监狱里的
He's not doing more time.
无论如何  他都会回监狱里去的  乔恩
One way or another, he's going back inside, Jon.
唯一需要讨论的就是刑期有多久
Only thing left to discuss is how long.
10年可没有讨论的余地
10 years is not a discussion.
那终身呢
How about life?
如果你真要法庭审理的话  你不会提供
If you really wanted to go to trial, you wouldn't be offering
我可一点儿都不怕发回重审
I'm not scared to go back to trial.
现在有DNA的证据
That DNA's out there now.
这个问题很难回答  多重抽样
Gonna be hard to answer for that, multiple samples.
他已经认罪了  记录在案的
And he confessed... on the record.
而且根据录音带里的声音
And it's gonna be hard to argue that it was coerced
很难证明他是被迫认罪
above the sound of the tape rolling,
他承认是他干的
The sound of him saying that he did it.
如果我们翻供呢
What if we get that confession thrown out?
如果你觉得我完全不可能
If you think I see zero chance
在庭审中让他被再次定罪
of getting another conviction at trial,
那我现在就告诉你那是不可能的
I'm here to dissuade you of that notion.
你和你的委托人
You and your client should be terrified
应该竭力避免上法庭
of stepping foot in a courtroom.
我现在是在救你
I'm throwing you a lifeline here.
有期徒刑10年以上
Time plus 10.
你该说声谢谢  然后去通知你的委托人
Now you say "Thank you," you go tell your client,
别自找麻烦
and you don't make this difficult.
我会和我的委托人商量的
I'll talk with my client.
最好如此  要快  不要声张
You do that -- quickly and quietly.
没那么多时间让你拖延
This isn't gonna be drawn out.
很抱歉让你错过了航班
Sorry to make you miss a flight.
普安那公园
他的车在这儿
His truck's here.
把啤酒拿上
Hey, grab them beers.
倒霉
Damn.
算他有种  我们大老远的来一趟
Boy's got a lot of nerve -- not being home
就为了跟他喝个酒他居然不在
after we drove all this way just to have a beer with him.
我想我们是该先打个电话的
Should have called, I guess.
我去看看后面
I'm gonna go check the back.
后门开着呢
Back door is open!
进来吧
Come on in.
他在吗
Is he here?
应该不在
Doesn't look like it.
那这样...
S-should we --
难道在这大太阳下等着吗  才不
Wait out here in the sun? No.
管他的呢  哥们儿  进来
Screw that, buddy. Come on.
你看过里屋了吗
Did you check in the back?
我都没打算找他
I didn't even think to.
乔治
Hey, George!
梅尔顿制药的好货色
Courtesy of Melton pharmaceuticals!
乔治不会介意的
George won't mind!
一向如此
It's like old times!
你怎么在这儿
Um... What are you doing?
我在喝酒做意面
Um... Drinking a beer, making spaghetti.
你错过航班了吗
Did you miss your flight?
给我个吻吧
Come kiss me.
到底怎么啦
What's going on?
过来
Come here.
怎么了
What?
你嗑药了吗
Are you high?
可能吧
Maybe.
阿曼莎·霍顿  你太不乖了
Amantha Holden, you rule breaker.
千万别告诉警长
Mm. Just don't tell Daggett.
我不说
Oh, I won't.
不过说真的  怎么了
No, but, seriously -- what's up?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
你不能说不能告诉我
You can't say you can't tell me.
我不该告诉你
I shouldn't tell you.
现在还不行
Not yet.
是什么事  乔恩
What is it, Jon?
他们又要抓他
They want to arrest him again.
-阿曼莎  -天哪
- Amantha. - Oh, my God.
-他们又要审讯他  我就知道  -不是
- They're gonna put him back on trial. I knew -- - No.
"不是"是什么意思
What do you mean "No"?
是什么
What?
他们想跟他签订认罪协议
They want to offer him a plea deal.
认罪协议
A plea deal?
他们想要什么
What do they want?
他们当然希望他认罪了
Well, they want him to plead guilty, obviously.
-然后呢  -然后
- And? - And...
有期徒刑10年以上
10 more years.
不  不行  去他的  乔恩
No. No! "F" that, Jon!
这事还有得商量  这才是开始
It can all be negotiated. That's just where they started.
等等
Wait.
他们想给我们条出路
They're offering a way out.
算是吧
Of sorts, yeah.
说明他们觉得自己赢不了
They don't think they can win.
要不然他们为什么这样呢
W-why else would they be talking like this?
不是这么简单的
You know it's not that simple.
丹尼尔也会觉得他们会输  给他打电话
Daniel's gonna think they're folding, too. Call him.
我一直在打
I have been.
但他就是不接
And he's not calling me back.
天哪  太扫兴了
God, what a buzzkill.
是啊
Yep.
参议员  卡尔
Senator. Carl.
你们怎么来了
This is a surprise.
你好吗  小泰
How you doing, Ted?
我不确定
I don't know yet.
小泰  我这也是迫不得已
Teddy, I want you to know that I absolutely felt like I had to.
天哪  卡尔
Christ, Carl.
为什么
Why?
只有我们  小泰
It's just us now, Teddy.
只有我们干什么
"Just us" what?
搞什么  卡尔
God damn it, Carl.
他并不想背叛你的信任  孩子
He didn't want to betray your confidence, son,
但必须如此
but it was the right thing to do.
这很不容易  但却是正确的事
It wasn't easy, but it was right.
对谁来说
Right for who?
我们希望你能站出来
We want you to come forward.
我们希望你起诉
We need you to press charges.
我绝不会起诉的
There's no way I'd do that.
绝对不会
No way in hell.
你得想想  丹尼尔下一个
You need to think about the next person
会伤害谁
that Daniel has a problem with.
你觉得他不会再干了吗
You think this was a two-time thing?
在他那样对汉娜后
What he did to Hanna?
在他那样对你后
What he did to you?
你觉得他会这么容易就收手吗
That he's gonna stop,
难道他会痊愈吗
like he's cured or something?
他有强迫症  小泰
He has these compulsions, Ted.
他没法控制自己
It's as if he can't help himself.
听着  我们那天吵架了
Look, we got in an argument that night,
事情有点失控
that has got out of hand.
仅此而已
That's all.
你继母呢
What about your stepmama?
你父亲  你弟弟呢
Your daddy, your -- your little brother?
他们都和他生活在一起不是吗
They're all living under the same roof with him, aren't they?
他绝不会伤害妈妈的
He'd never hurt mom.
那你妻子呢
And what about your wife?
你们吵架就是因为她吧
This little argument was about her, initially.
你不想让她身处危险吧
You don't want to put her in any future danger, do you?
我绝不会让那个混蛋再和她单独在一起
That son of a bitch is never gonna be alone with her again.
这点我可以保证
I can promise you that.
这会让我的家分崩离析的
This would rip my family apart.
会让他们崩溃
Rip them apart.
我妈
My mom...
我爸
My dad...
所有人
Everybody.
就全完了
It'd be over.
我理解你  孩子
I feel for you, son.
真的
I do.
但是这事不仅关乎你
But this is bigger than you --
甚至不仅关乎你的家人
bigger than your family, even.
换句话说  这不是你能控制的
In a way, it's -- it's out of your hands.
我们都无法控制
O-out of all of our hands.
是我编的
I made it up.
我是说
I mean, uh...
我们那天确实吵架了
we got into an argument that night.
这部分是真的
That -- that part's true.
但剩下的...
But the rest of it, I just...
都是我编的
made up.
你为什么要编这种事
Why would you make something like that up, son?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许是因为我喝醉了吧
'Cause I was drunk, I guess.
我错了
I made a mistake.
抱歉  但我要关店了
Now, if you'll all excuse me, I got to close the shop up.
这事不会就这么过去的  小泰
This ain't going away, Ted.
真相永远不会消失
The truth never does.
我说的就是真相
That is the truth.
请离开吧
Now, if you'll all excuse me...
营业时间
你觉得我们应该从塔尔博特家族入手吗
You think we ought to work our way up the Talbot family tree?
从泰德那里吗
Ted Sr.?
我不确定  罗兰
I don't know about that, Roland.
这事也由不得你
You don't have to.
我有个叔叔  就那样疯了
I had an uncle who went bat-shit -- just lost it.
一个表叔吧  应该是
A cousin, I guess it was -- is.
怎么疯的
How'd he lose it?
他是我父亲的远方表弟
He's my dad's second cousin.
现在很老了
He's old now.
所以也算你的远方表亲
So, he's your second cousin, too.
什么
What?
他是你父亲的远方表亲  所以就是你的
Your dad's second cousin is your second cousin,
只是隔了一代
only once removed.
算吧  有一天他就那么疯了
Anyway, he just lost it one day, man.
有时候会这样的
That can happen.
他曾经搞过艺术  有段时间还挺像回事的
He was, uh, artsy -- real artsy for a while.
不过在斯帕坦堡艺术也就那么回事儿
You know, however artsy you can be in Spartanburg.
他总是  在办展览
He was always, um, putting on plays
搞了很多西班牙式的东西
and... lots of Spanish stuff.
洛尔卡吗
Lorca?
也许吧  这不重要
Sure. Doesn't matter.
西班牙内战刚爆发一个月
Lorca was shot on the side of the road
洛尔卡就被人在路边枪杀了
a month into the Spanish civil war.
我父亲的表弟在1981年刚过了三天
Well, my dad's cousin stabbed a librarian in the face
就捅了一个图书管理员
three days into 1981.
摇头丸在哪里
Where's them mints at?
在我这里
Behind the at.
好吧
All right. Okay.
小小蛋形蓝色药丸
Little -- little egg-shaped blue one.
你也来一粒
Take you one.
他们好像不吃黄色的
Them yellows never took.
也许他们吃了
And maybe they did,
吃完后嗨大了
shake the cobwebs off.
现在几点了
What time is it?
管他几点了
You don't have to do time no more.
我得  我得打电话...
I'm gonna -- I'm gonna call...
你要打给谁
Who you got to call?
打给你妈吗
Your mama?
还真是啊
You do! You do!
你还得打电话跟你妈报告
You got to call your mama!
你就像那种时光机
You're -- you're like a time machine
但是只能穿越回过去
that don't go nowhere -- but backwards!
要我把音量调低点吗
Hey, you want me to turn down the jams?
这样她就不会担心你
So she's not worried about you
被别人带坏了吧
being around a bad element?
告诉她你自己就是个坏人
Tell her you are the bad element.
那时我只是个孩子
I was just a kid back then.
我一直不理解我的远房表亲为啥要那么做
I never understood why he did it -- my second cousin.
隔了一代的表亲
Once removed.
我记得当时家人都吓坏了
I remember my family being horrified.
那个我也不明白
Didn't understand that either.
真的
Be honest.
我倒不害怕
I wasn't horrified.
我当时想
I was like,
"要是我当时在场就好了"
"Wish I'd seen them plays."
你妈开心了吗
Mama happy now?
老兄  她就是个贱人
She was a bitch, man.
谁
Who?
汉娜
Hanna.
贱人  骚货
Bitch and a slut.
别这么说她
Oh, don't say that.
那不然我们来这干什么
Ain't that why we're here?
来填补你的记忆空白
To fill in the blanks?
你敢对天发誓你真的不记得了吗
You swear on a stack of Bibles you don't remember?
记得什么
Remember what?
到底发生了什么
What the hell happened?
不记得
No.
你不记得强奸她了吗
You don't remember raping her,
你兄弟乔治都作证了
like your buddy George testified?
我不记得强奸过她
I don't remember raping her, no.
那是因为你根本就没强奸她  丹尼尔
That's because you didn't rape her, Daniel.
老兄  你根本就没上她
You didn't even screw her, bud.
你都硬不起来
You couldn't get it up, man.
这部分你也不记得了吗
Or did you block out that part, too?
你怎么知道的
How would you know that?
你惊慌失措地逃跑了之后  她告诉我的
She told me -- after you ran off all weirded out.
她为什么要告诉你这些
Why would she tell you that?
汉娜13岁的时候我就破了她的处
I popped Hanna's cherry when she was 13.
好吧是她叔叔破的
Well, her uncle did before,
当然除了她的家人之外  我是第一个
but outside of family, I mean...
你在撒谎
You're lying.
我比你更了解她  丹尼尔
I knew her way better than you did, Daniel.
我一直不能理解为什么你觉得她很特别
I never understood why you thought she was so damn special.
她确实很特别
She was special.
好吧  哥们  她很特别
Okay, buddy. She was special.
但是你现在想起来
But you, uh, do remember
当时没有硬起来了吧
not being able to get it up now, don't you?
我不...
I don't...
知道
know.
当时我们在上面看了全过程
We were up there watching the whole thing --
你感到很尴尬所以你朝她吼了
you yelling at her 'cause you were embarrassed
而她在那笑
and her laughing.
当然她不是在嘲笑你
I mean, she wasn't laughing at you.
她就只是在笑  只是笑点低
She was just laughing. She was tripping.
她觉得一切都很好笑
Everything was funny to her,
尤其是你因为硬不起来而发怒
especially you all dick-puny mad.
我以为是她告诉你发生了什么
I thought she told you what happened,
而不是你亲眼看到了
not you saw what happened.
确实是她告诉我的
She did tell me.
你走之后  我们下来找她
See, we came down to her after you left --
她在毯子下还是全身赤裸着的
her still naked as a jaybird on that blanket.
那妹子真不喜欢穿衣服啊
That girl never did like clothes.
天啊
Oh, man.
你根本无法想象
You know, you just can't realize
一个十六岁少女在当时的我们眼里有多美
how pretty a 16-year-old girl is when you're that age.
我真希望我有一台只能穿回过去的时光机
I just wish I had me a backwards-only time machine.
闭嘴
Don't talk anymore.
好吧
Okay.
不说了
Sure, buddy.
就打算在这里傻等然后听听音乐
Want to just wait around and listen to music
等乔治来吗
and wait for George?
乔治不会来了
George ain't coming.
我压五块赌你猜对了
Betcha $5 you're right.
是你杀了她吗  特雷
Did you kill her, Trey?
得了吧
Come on, man.
你真以为我会自己说自己有罪吗
You really think I'd incriminate myself?
你一定是疯了
You might be wired or something.
我没有杀人动机  丹尼尔
I had no motive, Daniel.
她对我毫无意义
She didn't mean anything to me.
再说了  只要我想我随时都能搞定她
Besides that, I could have gotten it anytime I wanted.
所以我杀她有什么意义
So what would have been the point?
这事你谁都不能说
You can't tell anybody this.
可以保证吗
Swear?
保证
Sure.
我让老梅尔顿给我口过几次
I let old Melton suck me off a couple times back then,
身边缺姑娘的时候
when there were no girls around.
他曾经也很奇葩  就和你一样
He was a weird one, too -- weird as you.
曾经
"Was"?
"Was".
也许他做了什么治疗  我也不清楚
Maybe he's had therapy or something. I don't know.
但是乔治可能会杀了她
But, hell, George could have killed her.
他精神有点不正常
He had pt-up issues, man.
他拿大口径枪杀过一只猫
He shot a cat with a .410.
你在胡扯
You're full of shit.
不对  还是应该是你杀的
No, it had to be you.
不然不符合逻辑了
Nothing else is logical.
那你说为什么我不记得我做过  特雷
You tell me why I don't remember doing it, Trey,
如果你全部都弄明白了的话
if you have all the answers.
这问题可难不倒我
Well, that ain't the question that's bugging me.
我的问题是  如果你没做或者不记得了
My question is, why would you say that you did it
那为什么还说是你干的
if you didn't or if you didn't remember?
有段时间他们让我以为...
They made me believe that I had...
我做了
for a while.
让你以为  还是让你记起
Made you believe or made you remember?
算了  我相信你
You know what? I believe you.
我真的相信你
I actually believe you.
相信我什么
Believe what?
相信你什么都不记得了
That you don't remember.
但我还是不相信你没做过
But I sure as hell don't believe you didn't do it.
我看到你当时在上面看着我们
I saw you up there watching us.
我没在上面
I wasn't up there.
你在
Sure you were.
看她把什么都往脸上放...
With her grabbing everything put in her face --
看我们在抓挠  抚摸
Just grabbing it and touching it
亲吻还有口交  就好像这不是真的一样
and kissing it and sucking it like it wasn't even real.
闭嘴  特雷
Shut up, Trey!
我没有说这样不好  兄弟
I'm not saying it was a bad thing, man.
反倒还有点可爱
It was kind of cute, really.
她就完全放松了
I mean, her just being free, you know,
再也不用管那些狗屁道德伦理
and not caught up in any of that morality bullshit.
我觉得这么看的话她确实挺特别
I guess she kind of was special, in a way.
她不会这么做的
She wouldn't do that.
你有时候真是太老土了  丹尼尔
Damn, you're old-fashioned sometimes, Daniel.
你逼她这么做的
You forced her to do it.
逼她  她可享受呢
Forced her? Hell, she loved it.
我当时没在上面
I wasn't up there.
刚开始我以为你在调查
You know, at first, I thought you were digging on it,
但后来我发现你就呆在那里
but then, later, I realized you were paralyzed.
这不可能  不是这样的
That never happened. Not like that.
你知道吗
You know what?
要是我的话  我会下去
If it'd been me, I would have gone down there
杀掉每个和她交合的混蛋
and killed every son of a bitch who put anything inside of her.
可是你...
But you, man, you just...
你等我们走了之后
you just waited for us to leave,
反而把她杀了
and then you killed her instead.
你这个变态杀人狂
You're a psycho killer.
你看呀  看那边
I mean, look at that -- right there.
谁会把别人往墙上撞
I mean, who throws a guy into a wall?!
让我起来
Let me up!
Let me up!!
让开
Get off me.
我要让你去跟乔治解释
I'm gonna let you explain that to Georgey.
墙都是你弄坏的
That one's on you.
黄色的吃了有效果了吗
Is those yellows working?
我们再吃一粒
Let's take another one.
要记住
Remember?
本性难移
You are...who you are.
好吗
Okay?
永远都不会改变
It's forever.
就像印第安人永远都是印第安人
It's like being an Indian or something.
我了解你
I know you.
现在你也了解自己了
Now you know you.
只要你不是真的不记得了
If you ever really forgot.